<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trademark on Doctrine &amp; Data</title>
    <link>https://reichert.law/blog/tags/trademark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trademark on Doctrine &amp; Data</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://reichert.law/blog/tags/trademark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>World Champ Tech v. Peloton: House Marks, App Stores, and the Quiet Power of Context</title>
      <link>https://reichert.law/blog/posts/world-champ-tech-peloton-house-marks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://reichert.law/blog/posts/world-champ-tech-peloton-house-marks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking about &lt;em&gt;World Champ Tech v. Peloton&lt;/em&gt; because it quietly rearranges trademark doctrine. The Ninth Circuit&amp;rsquo;s memorandum tells a familiar story in a new setting, and in doing so, it makes a house-mark issue feel like a UI problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the quick orientation. World Champ Tech owns &amp;ldquo;BIKE+&amp;rdquo; for a cycling-metrics app. Peloton later launched &amp;ldquo;Peloton Bike+.&amp;rdquo; The dispute proceeds as a reverse-confusion case, meaning the concern is that the junior user&amp;rsquo;s scale erases the senior&amp;rsquo;s identity. The Ninth Circuit affirmed summary judgment for Peloton. So far, so ordinary. But the way the panel handled the house-mark issue is where things get interesting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Doctrine &amp; Data</title>
      <link>https://reichert.law/blog/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://reichert.law/blog/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;Doctrine &amp;amp; Data&lt;/em&gt;—a blog about intellectual property law through an empirical lens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Thomas Reichert, an IP attorney and Assistant Professor of Law at Southern Illinois University Simmons School of Law. My work sits at the intersection of legal doctrine and empirical analysis, asking a simple question: &lt;em&gt;Does the law work the way we think it does?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-this-blog-is-about&#34;&gt;What This Blog Is About&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Legal doctrine is full of multifactor tests, balancing frameworks, and totality-of-the-circumstances analyses. Courts and practitioners treat these frameworks as if every factor matters, as if the careful weighing of numerous considerations is what produces just outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
